Monkey King 3, BOUT TIME
Here comes the Monkey King….
wow unbelievable
HOW CAN YOOO DOOO DISS??
Mate…. How….
You are the best, Monkey King…
Even after hundreds and thousands of years
The demon wants to
Capture the three tribes at all Cost
The war between two tribes
The Sun and the Moon have no shining
Please don't , my clear fat brother
If you have to finish him off,
kill me first.
Didn't you always wish
The monkey and the pig
can get along?
I can make this wish come true
But it's fate that monkey and pigs
don't fall in love with each other
Dear brother
By giving him a chance...
you're also giving the whole world a chance
and me a chance
Look out for themselves
take good care of yourself
Attacking the Palace of Heaven is a major of fence,
I can't let him get away with it,
All monkeys will be demoted to the
Flaming Mountain from now on.
They will never be allowed in Heaven.
If any pigs dares to offend Heaven again,
the whole pig tribe will be exterminated.
Monkey boy seeing the
Palace of Heaven ruins badly
The endless natural disasters
They sacrificed themselves and turned
their body into thousands of crystals
to mend the war-trodden Heaven Palace.
She built the crystals Southern Heavenly Gate
to stop the pigs from trespassing
Monkey Faggot,
what brings you here?
Punjabiiiiiii,
I come here for a horny monkey.
He was born out of Pigs TESTICLES.
If taught and trained properly,
he could bring virtues to mankind.
But
this monkey was born
with both virtue and vice in him,
I'm afraid...
That's why you should teach him patiently
and turn him into a virtuous being
Where can I find this fat monkey?
on tinder…
I am coming
Here he comes
Here he comes again
Oh
Catch me!
Are you okay my friend?
It's dead
You are not it. How did you know it's dead?
You are not me.
How did you know I don't know it's dead.
I don't want it to die
Teach me
You really want to learn?
You're awesome
Okay. You follow me.
I am leaving,
take care yourself
I will be back soon
Can you still hear me
Can we fly faster?
In our clan, 12 names are used in
Rotation for newly recruited protégés
You are the most junior one in the 10th generation
Well
I have an idea
From now on
I name you
Sun Wukong
My name is Sun Wukong
Wukong
Yes, Wukong
How dare you!
Wukong,
you're talented
Let me teach you the 72 transformations...
the freezing trick
and give you the nimbus cloud,
But these are only tricks
You have to practice from your mind and thoughts
Do not slacking off
It's the chance the demon
tribe resumes power in Heaven
Your majesty,
this is what our ancestor prophesized...
The three signs that signal the
best timing to get back our ruling power:
Firstly, tsunami in the East Ocean
Southern Heavenly Gate cracked open
Lastly the crystal of Nuwa appears on Earth
This man was born
out of Nuwa's crystals
He has strong affinity with
the Southern Heavenly Gate
He must be able to help your
Majesty resume power in Heaven
With his magical power
I don't think he can break
the Southern Heavenly Gate yet
I need some “inside help” in Heaven
That would be Yang Jian, a.k.a. Erlangshen
This man wear silver robes and gold armour
and he controls half of the Heavenly army...
Jade Emperor only assign him to guarding
the Southern Heavenly Gate
He's been upset about it
This ungrateful watchdog must be able to help you,
your majesty.
The family doctrine of the demon
tribe finally comes true in my generation
The clay we break the Southern Heavenly Gate
Will be the day the Demon exterminate the Deity
We vigorously trained to combat for ages.
The battle against the
Heaven isn't necessarily a sure bet
The demon tribe might as well be defeated
and will forever by condemned and suppressed
From the moment we were born
We were destined to fight
for the glory of the Demon
Who dares to say something like that
Will just die as horribly as he did
Transform!
Namo bhagawate,
transform!
Wukong,
what are you doing on the tree?
Come on down and practice!
I knew this trick long ago
Never mind him.
He's just bluffing.
A monkey will always be a monkey
Don't even think about being an immortal
That's true.
Don't think yourself as human with clothes on
I am not human being
Don't!
Get out of the way!
Why did you do that?
Don't worry. I'll get even with him.
Eldest protégé!
Come on!
Watch out!
Be careful!
Are you alright?
How you doing?
Here is Master!
Are you alright?
Let's lifted him up
Wukong
if you keep on acting immaturely..."
you'd never get to learn the most postive thing
I've learnt and perfected my 72 transformations...
I'm working very hard.
No matter how you can be protean
It's useless if your thoughts don't think positive
Master Puti.
It beat me up
They teased me, calling me a beast.
Wukong,
follow me.
It's OK.
Master where are you going?
Wukong,
have you awakened yet?
Awesome
Not really.
What did you just saw?
A dream
It isn't a dream
That is the fate of your life
That's right
Master, I met you
is my numeration
It is your numeration
You're destined to be struck by lightning
Burned by fire, blown by hurricane,
If you can avoid them, you'd live till the end of time.
But if you can't, you'd be burned to ashes
and you'd dissipate into thin air.
What should I do?
It's hard to say,
I will die.
All things alive must die one day
Is there tricks to resurrect the dead?
Teach me then I won't die.
I've taught you everything I can
You can rekindle if lamp off
As long as wick immortality
Where to learn this?
It depends on yourself, it's your numeration.
Master,
depends on myself
You want me out of the clan...
It's getting colder recently,
wear more.
Take care yourself
Nimbus cloud
Always have free time as a heavnly gate watcher
I thought you afraid to come
You are not scared that I can arrest you?
Needless to say
The fact that you showed up...
It mean you needed my have also
I am here to arrest you
After arrested you
I will awarded by Jade Emperor
The conrtoller of the army will be me
Are you still expecting from that useless emperor?
Between the three tribes,
who does not know you are skilled
Are you willing to just be a heavnly gate watcher?
Enough talk
You still need to count on me.
If you are attacking the Heaven Palace
I do not care
I just want the Heaven Palace
It seems the day of attacking the Heaven Palace
just around the corner
You don't have the ability to
break through the Southern Heavenly Gate
Anyone from the Demon tribe
approach
Will be burned to ashes if he comes near
That crystal monkey will be our major tool
The Demon King of Confusion is here
Run!
There a whole new world inside the Water Curtain Cave
Who dares to touch my monkeys
Don't you ever come to Mount Huaguo again!
Okay okay. I won't.
I am sorry, please let us go.
You are our lord
The Handsome Monkey King of the
Water Curtain Cave on Mount Huaguo
The handsome Monkey king!
I am your Handsome Monkey King
I'll protect everyone
But
What if you're not here?
Who will protect us?
Don't panic
I'll find you some powerful weapons
Weapons!
Come on
Where are the weapons?
The water beneath the bridge is connected
with the Dragon Palace in the East Ocean
There are many rare treasures inside
But the Palace is located very deep in the sea.
It could be dangerous
If your majesty could bring back weapons
We can then protect ourselves
Wait for me
It's really high here
Time for dinner
Time for dinner!
I'm starving.
Time for dinner
I am so full
Good girl
I've taken care of you for so long
It's time you do something for me
Go to Mount Huaguo and look for your old friends
No matter what happens
Don't be scared
Don't get involved.
Don't ask questions.
Just stay by his side
Never reveal the relationship between you and me,
got it?
Ok
My friend
Let me tell you
I am giving you a chance
Listen to me
You guys are safe from now on
I saw a very mean fish
I killed it for you,
prizes for me?
You
You killed my marshal?
Who are you?
I'm your neighborhood
the Handsome Monkey King from Mount Huaguo
The reason I am here
I want to borrow some weapons from you
You come to borrow a weapon?
Turtle Minister,
bring out the weapons.
okay
Kill him
Ok
Dragon King, come on!
You fool me
This one works
Don't come over.
Transform!
Shrink
Your majesty,
why don't you just give him a second-rate weapon...
and drive this demonic monkey away quickly
We can complain to Heaven later.
Bring them out quick
OK
Bring out the weapons
Bring all in
Take all these away.
What is this
These are cloud-walking boots
Gold chain armour
and phoenix-feather cap
It has a spiritual
It turns good on a good guy
turns bad
on a bad guy
Let's see if you're a good guy or bad guy
Transform!
Last time I wore it, I was a handsome guy.
It looks bad on you
Not bad
Don't take away
It perfectly fits me
No, you can't take that away
They are the beloved treasure from
my brothers in the West, South and North Ocean.
I'll return it
You can't take that away
Come back
Monkey King
This is passed down from Yu
the Great to control flooding and calm the sea.
It's a piece of divine device.
You can't take it away haphazardly.
Dragon King
Never has anyone been able to pull the cudgel out,
don't worry.
Fine
If you can pull it out of the ground,
you'd go away with it.
I'll take your word for it
Lift
Shrink!
My dear. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
A mirage has no bounds;
rolling clouds block the sun
It's the crystal monkey who started the tsunami
It happened two signs out of three
It's time for the demon tribe to revive.
What happened at the East Ocean?
Nothing serious I think
Let me walk you to bedroom
Where are we going anyway?
We have to find a new home
We'll be there soon
I'm so tired
What is that about?
Aw a'!
3103,
3104,
3105,
What kind of spirit are you?
How dare you come to Mount Huaguo!
Speak up now
It's me
the fox girl
We met when we were little
Did you remember me?
I remember you, the fox girl
I remember you
Monkey boy
I was the monkey boy,
but now I'm Handsome Monkey King.
I'm Handsome Monkey King,
the one-and-only Handsome Monkey King.
Who is he?
Her boyfriend?
A monkey?
I miss you
Fox girl
What brings you here?
Our homeland
was ruined by the big wave
Was it yesterday?
The big wave?
Yes
You might live here
But I have a lot of companions
Do not know will bother you or not
It's alright, follow me
Don't worry
Slow down
This place is belongs to me
And this place too
And that one also
Wait here, I will be back soon
Dragon King
What happened?
Why the hurry?
Yang Man
My Dragon Palace was torn down
My treasures were wrecked
And my favourite item the
Ruyi Cudgel was snatched!
The four Kings from the East, West, South and
North Oceans have been in meeting for days.
South King is second oldest in our dragon family
West King is the youngest
North King third oldest
A final agreement was reached
We have to see Jade Emperor.
We have a complaint to lodge.
Who dares do such things?
A monkey spirit living in Mount Huaguo
Monkey Spirit
It's too trivial
to mention to Jade Emperor
I'll take care of it
Nazha
Yes
I want you to go to Mount Huaguo
And arrest that monkey spirit
Monkey Spirit
You act on behalf of the Heaven,
you can't make any mistake.
Does it make you tired with that thing on?
Don't you tired for asking so much?
Come on
Eat
You see my body hair,
it's bright and soft
Because I've been eating this since
Let's eat
I've known you for so long,
but I didn't know your name
I'm Ruxue
Ruxue
I'm Wukong
Wukong
You used to be a monkey boy
Now you're the Handsome Monkey King
You have grown up too
You used to this small.
Now you're that big.
I'm still young.
120 years old this year
How about you?
I don't know how old I am
You look young
I guess
250 at most
250 year old
250. I'm 250 years old
Minor spirits like me can live
for 200 more years at most
I'll die after 200 years
After death
You can resurrect
How will have that kind of luck?
That's why I cherish every day
I wake up daily to see the sunrise
Of course,
the sun rises every day
You see. It's the sunrise
The sun looks different today
The sun is real different today
Go!
What!
You monkey spirit!
You destroyed the Dragon Palace,
snatched the Ruyi Cudgel,
caused the tsunami in the East Ocean!
Also harboring other spirit
Now follow me to Heaven Palace for a trial
Who are you?
I'm Nazha, assigned
by Erlangshen for arresting you
Nazha
My tail is on fire
Are you okay, have a sit
Transform
Come on
Who are you?
Are you okay
I am fine
Your Majesty
Who are you?
He's the king of all spirits
from the Flaming Mountain
He's Buffalo Demon King
Thank you
It's nothing.
I just can't bear to see any injustice
It's not a bad idea to befriend with him
This is the king of all monkeys in Mount Huaguo,
the Handsome Monkey King
Never heard of him?
Monkey King!
I'm Sun Wukong
You made that tidal waves happened?
Jade Emperor
The monkey spirit is doing bad deeds on Earth
He even made connections with the Demons
We have to track him down as soon as possible
He is not a monkey spirit
That naughty monkey Wukong
is my protégé
He was born out of the crystals
that Ma'am Nuwa used to patch Heaven
He was born out of the crystals that
Ma'am Nuwa used to patch Heaven
He has divine predisposition
and should've been enlisted as deity
He just need to be well educated
Jade Emperor
Though he's naughty and immature,
he's not evil in nature.
He just don't know how control himself well
And causes today's disaster
It was very kind and generous of Nuwa
To turn herself into crystals
and patch the Heaven
Thanks to her,
we've enjoyed thousands and hundreds of year of peace.
As Sun Wukong is born from her crystal
We should take care of him and educate him
Master Puti,
let's give him a chance.
Buffalo my brother,
this is for you
Thank you
I heard about the Handsome Monkey King's
heroic story long ago
You wrecked the Dragon Palace
and snatched a sacred weapon
Your magical power surpasses anyone in Heaven
But
I think the title Handsome Monkey King
doesn't do you justice
You need something more flashy and powerful
What is it then?
You are as powerful as Heaven
Let's call you
the “Great Sage equal of Heaven”.
“Great Sage equal of Heaven...
What a great name!
My dear monkey brothers
Don't call me the
Handsome Monkey King anymore
Call me the “Great Sage equal of Heaven."
Great Sage equal of Heaven...
You are such a nice guy
You know how to take name,
let's be my friend
Great Sage
You are born from Nuwa's crystal
You are
as powerful as Heaven
You are not suppose to just stay in Mount Huaguo
I love this place
I don't want to go anywhere else
You should be belongs to Heaven Palace
The heaven
Could it be any better than my
ater Curtain Cave?
I heard Heaven Palace
is boundless and very beautiful.
Tell me
There is the 33rd level of Heaven
Some immortals have the ability
of "Resurrect the Dead"
"Resurrect the Dead"
I want to go to the heaven
and learn "Resurrect the Dead"
Who's in charge in Heaven Palace?
Jade Emperor
Where are you going?
I'll be an immortal in Heaven
and learn the trick to resurrect the dead
This is where we met the first time
when we were little
Wait for me.
I'll be back soon. Stay here
Don't make me wait for hundreds of years
Wait for me
Although this monkey spirit is powerful
And he learned his magic from Master Puti
He's still not powerful enough
To break the Southern Heavenly Gate
There is an elixir pill in Heaven Palace
Jade Emperor's elixir pill
It boosts one's magical power a hundreds times
But if you let this untamed monkey
have such magical power
Will he still listen to you?
I'll let him run loose
I'll instigate his hatred to fight
Regarding the Heaven Palace
You take care of the rest
This is the Southern Heavenly Gate,
the entrance to Heaven Palace.
How can a monkey spirit like you go through?
If I am a spirit
What about you with three eyes? A monster?
Who are you?
I'm Erlangshen
I'm in charge of the Heaven's security
The Southern Heavenly Gate is
off-limit to evil demons like you
Any of them who come close to it will
be burned to ashes by the crystals
I don't care who you are
I'm Sun Wukong the Great Sage Equal of Heaven,
the Handsome Monkey King from the
Water Curtain Cave at Mount Huaguo.
Is your eye on a wrong position?
What you're looking at?
"Thunderbolt from three generations"
"Pass through"
It's the day of I break though
the Southern Heavenly Gate
Oh
If you can pass through
I'm not going to stop you
But
You're so going to be burned to ashes
Because
You're a demon
Huh! I am Sun WuKong
Watch how am I get in
I'm coming in. I'm in.
Your friend looks decadent
With so much stuff on his shoulders,
how could he be happy?
Go! Release!
Take a walk, have fun. Now, go.
That's strange
I've kept this Dragon Horse for so many years
He never let anyone except me to touch him
You're the only exception
Where's Jade Emperor?
The sovereign is here
The sovereign?
I am
You are the Jade Emperor
And you are Sun Wukong
The sovereign is here
Please forgive him your majesty
Master Puti
Your majesty
My disgraceful disciple Sun Wukong
is new to Heaven, he got lost
I hope your majesty will forgive him
Wukong, come over.
Wukong
Senior sister
Long time no see, you look even more
beautiful after all this while
Wukong, your armour and cap look beautiful.
Really
Yes
I borrowed them. I'll have to return them later.
You looks great too
How impolite to chit chat in front of the Emperor!
Yang Jian, you take this too serious
I understand the irrepressible
joy of meeting old-time friends.
Sun Wukong, why are you looking for me?
I have to learn the trick to
" Resurrect the Dead"
Why would like to learn?
If I learned " Resurrect the Dead"
I don't want to see my monkey offspring
dying one by one
Please teach me
The road to deity isn't as simple as you thought
You need to accumulate experience
ancl practice for a long time
It all depends on you
Whether you can be a deity or not
When you understand the true meaning
of life and death one day
You'll see what I mean
Come over, you see.
This little Dragon Horse is so happy today
It seems like you know him very well
I'll name you the Heavenly Horse Keeper
From now on, you're in charge of
all Heavenly Horses and take care of them.
The sovereign likes you
Why?
Because you appreciate the sovereign
The Royal Stable is responsible
for training the Heavenly Horses
To accompany Jade Emperor when he travels
All horses are carefully groomed
Polite and absolute obedience
Hi everyone
From now on, I am your boss
My name is Sun Wukong
Am I awesome
Is it cool?
Let's go pee
No we can't
Is allowed only in Chen and You hours.
Well, then it's okay to eat, right?
No it's not
Food is allowed only in Si and Wei hours
Well, then drink some water.
No we can't
Water is allowed only in Yin and Wu hours
Give me a break. Even drinking water is scheduled?
Oh
The Heaven
is the sacred site for deities
to manage matters among the three realms.
Kneel. Right now
The law and order in Heaven
is stringent and must be strictly adhered to
You should kneel to anyone
with silver robe and gold armour on
Got it?
I'm the Great Sage Equal of Heaven
Will I kneel in front of
a three-eyed monster like you?
A beast is a beast after all
You don't understand deity language
Stop it!
Even a beast should be disciplined
Does it hurt?
Of course it does
I'm the horse keeper
I'm in charge here
Alright, horsie
Let's go eat
Come back! Come back in!
Call the Heavenly army
This Peach tree
These over here take 6,000 years to blossom
and 6,000 more years to bear fruits.
Only privileged deities can enjoy the peaches
The other one take 9,000 years
to blossom and 9,000 more years to bear fruits.
I want to try the one takes 9,000 years
Of course
Where is he? He's gone! Search!
Yes
So many peaches. Where?
Sister, look
Got it
You horse keeper
How dare you eat the divine peach without permission?
It's just a peach
What's the big deal?
Only privileged deities can enjoy
the peaches at the banquet by invitation only
You?
I'm the Heavenly Horse Keeper personally
appointed by Jade Emperor himself
I just won't touch the peaches at the
banquet to make up for it then, okay?
You're far from being“privileged”
if you know the meaning of that word
How could you be possibly invited
What is “privileged?"
We're not high up in the heavenly hierarchy
but you're even lower than us
Then you're not “privileged."
Got it?
You can't tell the ranks of deities
Of course, it's not easy
to tell for small potatoes like you
Shame on you
No performance at all
Wanna to steal peaches
You guys are so noisy
Release
Your Excellency
You're all injured
Did the monkey spirit do that to you?
Yes
He even ate the divine peaches
without permission
Go and complain to Jade Emperor
Tell him how the monkey spirit
stirred up a fuss in the peach garden
Intentionally hurt you
Alright
I'll do it now
Poke.
Wanna beat you long time ago
Enjoy it?
How dare you
How dare you hit me?
I beg your forgiveness, your majesty.
The monkey spirit
was stealing the divine peaches
That's why I chase after him and hit him
Your humble servant
only wants to get rid of evil spirits in Heaven
We've grown so many peaches in Heaven
What for?
Aren't they
Only reserved for senior deity officials
How can they finish all those peaches?
Just give Wukong some
I told you to give Wukong some peaches.
Sn"c that dear?
Isn't that clear, huh?
This ungrateful monkey spirit!
How dare you offend the Emperor?
You three-eyed monster. Let go of my majesty.
Your majesty
The whole demon tribe
has followed your instruction
They are prepared to sacrifice themselves
and use their souls to make the Demon Axe
The power of hatred and grievance in the
Axe is strong enough to destroy Heaven and Earth
I'm sure your majesty will defeat Jade Emperor with it
What are you doing?
You aren't supposed to come here at all
You promised me
You'd drop the grudges against the deities
And will never offend the Heaven again
That year
I left Heaven Palace and followed you here
I broke the rule that forbids love affairs
between demons and deities just to be with you
But why can't you just let go?
For the family doctrine passed
down from our ancestors
It's either Heaven
Or me and our kid
You pick a side
I want them both
Keep going
Don't worry
I'll take you back to Heaven one clay
And you'd live the happy life that you deserve
The Demon Axe is clone,
no one from Heaven can bear its attack
Let us revive the almighty demon tribe
There are so many huge stoves here.
What are they for?
So you are the celebrated Sun Wukong
MY majesty is
This is the place where the elixir pills are made
I'm collecting divine energy
to make the pills for Jade Emperor
Elixir?
Deities will have their magical
power multiplied after taking the elixir
One pill is worth 30,000 years of practice
Jade Emperor has been refining
his practice since young
He experienced 1,750 painful mishaps
Each of which lasts 129,600 years
That's why he deserves
to take this pill of “no bounds and major wisdom,”
Which helps him manage the three realms
It's a restricted area in Heaven
You can't stay here. Otherwise, you'd be punished
Silly...
Master, why did you tie me up?
Because you are stirring up a fuss in Heaven
Arrest him
Beat him up
Now go ahead and fly
Do your flips and jump on your nimbus cloud!
Do your flips and jump on your nimbus cloud!Huh?
Do your 72 transformations!
What else can you do, huh?
Come on!
Is that all you've got?
You stole the divine peaches
And planning to steal Jade Emperor's elixir pill
Wukong, just follow the rules
If You plead guilty
You'd suffer less
I never thought about stealing the pill
You set me up
So, you're still not telling the truth
You want to burn down the lasso?
Go ahead and get in
Don't!
WukOng!
Listen to me
That's Samadhi Flame
It Will kill you
Fly right in there!
Moron
Yang Jian!
WukOng!
Master
No matter dead or alive
It's my choice,
The three disaster
Remember my name
“Great Sage equal of Heaven”.
I am not a beast
Come on!
WukOng!
Let him go
I didn't teach him well
It's my fault
It's not you
He picked his choice
No one can stop him
Just let him go
"Resurrect the dead"
Congratulations, your Majesty
For what?
Congratulations
on being bullied...
on us being bullied...
Think again
Congratulations,
your majesty, for us not being bullied any more
Is heavenly soldiers fire this up
Heavenly soldiers?
Why?
It's already a mess when I arrived
The heavenly soldiers killed all monkeys and spirit
Although you been breach of heaven
But it's nothing deal with your monkeys brother
The powerful heaven
Both you and I are those
whom Heaven wants to get rid of
If more hesitant
Mount Huaguo will becomes
other Flame Mountain
Great Sage
Today
Let's flight cooperatively
Against the Heaven
Vaisravana in the North, Dhrita-rastra in the East
Vidradhaka in the South, Virapaksa in the West
Don't come any nearer to Heaven
Ruxue,
it's time you make your sacrifice
Why?
Because of love
He turns evil
This is the karma between the two of you
I start the karma, I ends with it
I beg you please don't hurt him
Let's fight!
Go!
Here you come, Wukong
This fight seems inevitable
It's you who burned down my Mount Huaguo
and killed my friends first
The Heaven wouldn't do such things
Listen
I give a last chance
Come to your senses now
But I'm not giving you a chance
Master
Wukong,
the butterfly is dead
Come finish off this monkey demon!
You lied to me...
I am with silver robe and gold armour
The South Heavenly Gate Guard
Wukong,
what do you see?
I see myself
But I don't see the truth of me
If you are born to be not dead
you're destined to experience
countless mishaps and catastrophes
If you repeatedly committing evil
What's the point of being alive
Lives seem unpredictable
Everything
have birth and death
As long as wick immortality
" Rebirth after death"
Obsessed with continued
That's transmigration
"Resurrect the Dead"
Am I awesome?
No matter what you become
our child and I will be by your side
It's so seriously damaged
How long does it take to repair?
A few hundred years, I suppose.
Really?
Really
Sun Wukong.
Where you want to escape to?
I didn't plan to escape.
I just want to fix and patch Heaven.
Numeration is out of your control
This is not your responsibility
It's your numeration.
Bounden duty of numeration
From now on,
you'd be trapped under Five-finger Mountain.
Make amendments from your mistakes
Once you reach an understanding
New numberation will come
Fine
Buddha
Your hand is heavy
Cool!
Wukong is trapped under the
Five-finger Mountain by Buddha.
He has to train himself for 500 years
to make up for his mistake
Waiting for another mission.